[Music]
what's up guys Justin coming to you I'm
here at the shop today and I wanted to
do a little product review on something
that I have been taking for a little
while now and I like it I like it it is
called mutant mass now they've got a
couple different flavors triple
chocolate vanilla ice cream I'm sure
there's a strawberry banana around here
yes I would have a man have some good
stuff so basically I wanted to tell you
guys this is not your normal weight game
all right this is not full of sugar and
trash all right okay look look at this
look at this nutrition facts here look
at four scoops a thousand sixty calories
now looking at sugar down there 34 and
four scoops are only 34 grams of sugar
now look at them carbs 182 grams for
four scoops there yeah you're 52 grams
of protein even get some extra bonus and
some calcium some iron it's good stuff
now there's 14 grams of fat in this
there's a ton of carbs for gaining
weight this is not what I would say
would be a stand alone product this is
not like a meal replacement
that's the stuff you want to drink with
your meal add a scoop in that's an if
you have even four meals a day and you
add a scoop in for your four meals to
something you're drinking that's next a
thousand calories a day now if you're
already eating 3,000 calories boom 4,000
plus another 182 grams of carbs and
another 50 freaking 50 grams of protein
it's pretty damn good now if you want to
get real creative you can throw another
protein shake together I personally like
doing like a oatmeal
protein oatmeal actually banana nut
protein oatmeal quicker good so I
put two packs of the Quaker Oatmeal in
there I'll put two scoops of the math in
there the mutant mask which is legit
stuff and I'll throw a protein powder in
there and I've got an awesome gainer
shake and I usually take that with my
breakfast great right off the bat carbs
and if you want to take it right if you
run like a keto diet take it like right
after your workout that's great cards
right after your workout they're going
straight into the muscle you're not
having no overfill or spillage of your
carbs and you're not storing them as fat
either right after your workout so
mutant mass is good stuff they hit it on
the nail a came and talked so excited I
came and talked they hit the nail on the
head with that stuff that this stuff is
awesome all right it's awesome check out
your local nutrition shop I'm here at
Rex's in Fremont it's good stuff we got
it later
[Music]